<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Charles-Antoine de Salaberry</title>
    <link>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Charles-Antoine de Salaberry</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:00:41 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fedora on the HP Envy 15 1067NR</title>
      <link>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/posts/fedora-on-the-hp-envy-15-1067nr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 20:00:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/posts/fedora-on-the-hp-envy-15-1067nr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A collection of Fedora 20 optimisations for my current setup (the SSD in a OCZ Vertez 3 120Go). Notice that most of my tweaks come from fedy, an excellent open source tool that does pretty much everything needed to get a more user friendly OS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Quick Bio I was born and raised in Paris, France. My interest in computers came pretty early when we received our first Windows 95 desktop computer at home. For some reason I was mesmerized by loading bars. I started a hunt for the biggest loading bars you can find. It eventually led me to reinstalling the operating system and switching the main home computer to Knoppix. Oh how it made my sims-fanatic sister rage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cadeesalaberry.github.io/readme/</guid>
      <description>C-A de Salaberry Personal README Inspired by Adrien Joly&amp;rsquo;s README, this text aims at introducing myself and sharing some information that may be helpful for us to break the ice, communicate, collaborate and adjust expectations effectively.
In it, I share my professional and personal values, what drives me, what makes me grumpy, and what my workflow looks like.
Random facts  I&amp;rsquo;m driven by efficiency and improvement in general. This makes me exigent with others, but also with myself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
